[
    {
        "option1": "The softest person gets the painest.",
        "option2": "The most softest person gets most pain.",
        "option3": "The softest person gets the most pain.",
        "option4": "Most pain gets the softest person.",
    "question": "সবচেয়ে নরম মানুষ সবচেয়ে বেশী কষ্ট পায়",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "The teacher know the height of both the most tallest and the most shortest boys.",
        "option2": "Height of both the tallest and the shortest boys the teacher knows.",
        "option3": "The teacher knows the heights of both the most tallest and the most shortest boys.",
        "option4": "The teacher knows the heights of both the tallest and the shortest boys.",
        "question": "সবচেয়ে লম্বা আর সবচেয়ে বেঁটে ছেলে দুজনেরই উচ্চতা শিক্ষকটি জানেন",
        "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "I come.",
        "option2": "I am come.",
        "option3": "I am coming.",
        "option4": "I coming.",
        "question": "আমি আসছি",
        "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "He/ She comes.",
        "option2": "He/ She has come.",
        "option3": "He/ She have come.",
        "option4": "He/ She is coming.",
        "question": "সে এসেছে",
        "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "They were come.",
        "option2": "They come.",
        "option3": "They have came.",
        "option4": "They came.",
        "question": "তারা এসেছিল",
        "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "You sing in bathroom.",
        "option2": "You singing in bathroom.",
        "option3": "In bathroom you sang.",
        "option4": "You are singing in bathroom.",
        "question": "তুমি চানের ঘরে গান করছ",
        "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "We have saw a ghost.",
        "option2": "We seen a ghost.",
        "option3": "We have seen a ghost.",
        "option4": "We saw a ghost.",
        "question": " আমরা একটা ভূত দেখেছি",
        "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Salils' wife has made for us good tea.",
        "option2": "Salil's wife made good tea for us.",
        "option3": "Salil's wife has made good tea for us.",
        "option4": "Salil's wife made good tea for we.",
        "question": "সলিলের স্ত্রী আমাদের জন্য ভালো চা তৈরী করেছিলেন",
        "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Why are you laughing ?",
        "option2": "Why you are laughing ?",
        "option3": "Why are you laugh ?",
        "option4": "Why laughing you are ?",
        "question": "তোমরা কেন হাসছ ?",
        "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "I liked to eat the chocolate.",
        "option2": "I like to eat the chocolate.",
        "option3": "I have liked to eat the chocolate.",
        "option4": "I have like to eat the chocolate.",
        "question": "আমার চকোলেটটা খেতে ভালো লেগেছে",
        "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Husband and wife hoped to see nice scenery.",
        "option2": "The husband and the wife have hoped to see nice scenery.",
        "option3": "The husband and the wife hope to saw nice scenery.",
        "option4": "The husband and the wife hoped to see nice scenery.",
        "question": "স্বামী-স্ত্রী সুন্দর দৃশ্য দেখার আশা করেছিল",
        "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Are we not going there to play ?",
        "option2": "Have we not gone to play to there ?",
        "option3": "We are not going to play there ?",
        "option4": "Are we going there not to play ?",
        "question": "আমরা কি ওখানে খেলতে যাচ্ছি না ?",
        "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    }
]